Finding Aid for Bureau of Government Library (University of Michigan) records, 1935-1980
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Bureau of Government Library (University of Michigan) records 1935-1980
University of Michigan. Bureau of Government Library.
87106 Bimu C448 2
Records, 1935-1980, of the Bureau of Government Library. Include clipping file, pamphlet file, and student papers relating to public administration and politics in Michigan.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
57 linear feet
The records were transferred from the Bureau of Government Library (donor no. 2807 ) when the library closed in 1986.
The record group is open without restriction.
The Bureau of Government was established in 1913 as a division of the Department of Political Science under the name Bureau of Reference and Research in Government. The title was changed to Bureau of Government in 1918. In 1934, the Bureau was reorganized into a separate unit of the university. Since 1938, the bureau was part of the University Institute of Public and Social Administration in the graduate school. The scope of the library's collection centered on Michigan materials. In 1947, the Bureau of Government Library came under a general library system. The records, comprising a clipping file, a pamphlet file and student papers, were transferred to the Bentley Library when the Bureau of Government Library closed in 1986.
The Records are arranged in three series: Clippings, Pamphlets, and Student Papers.
Subjects:
Michigan--Politics and government--1929-1938.; Michigan--Politics and government--1939-1945.; Michigan--Politics and government--1946-1960.; Michigan--Politics and government--1961-1970.; Michigan--Politics and government--1971-1980.; Michigan--Politics and government--1837-1950.; Michigan--Politics and government--1951-
- Clippings
  - A-B
    - Accident Prevention 1963-1979 (Box 1)
    - Adult Education 1947-1960 (Box 1)
    - Advertising, Regulation of 1954-1979 (Box 1)
    - Aged 1981 (Box 1)
    - Agriculture 1976-1979, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Airports
      - Michigan 1940-1979, 6 folders (Box 1)
      - Ann Arbor 1946-1979 (Box 1)
      - Detroit and Wayne County 1940-1979 (Box 1)
      - Lansing 1959-1979, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Air Pollution, 195-1980, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Alcoholism 1965 (Box 1)
    - Ambulances 1960-1979 (Box 1)
    - Annexation of Territory
      - Michigan 1947-1978 (Box 1)
      - Ann Arbor 1946-1979, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Lansing (metropolitan area) 1950-1967, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Battle Creek 1959-1965 (Box 1)
      - Grand Rapids 1959-1962 (Box 1)
      - Kalamazoo 1955-1962 (Box 1)
      - Ypsilanti 1950-1965 (Box 1)
    - Art and State 1962-1964, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Assessments
      - Ann Arbor 1952-1979 (Box 1)
      - Michigan 1941-1980, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Washtenaw County 1966-1980 (Box 1)
      - Detroit 1964-1971 (Box 1)
      - Lansing 1962-1970 (Box 1)
      - Ypsilanti 1958-1962 (Box 1)
    - Atomic Power 1955-1980 (Box 1)
    - Audits 1955-1980 (Box 1)
    - Automation 1957-1961 (Box 1)
    - Ballots 1964-1980, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Banks and Banking 1965-1979 (Box 1)
    - Billboards 1952-1978 (Box 1)
    - Bonds (Box 2)
      - Michigan 1959-1977 (Box 2)
      - Municipal 1946-1979 (Box 2)
    - Boundaries 1965-1980 (Box 2)
    - Bridges 1956-1980, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Budget Administration 1936-1961 (Box 2)
      (see also Fiscal Administration)
    - Budgets
      - State 1946-1980, 4 folders (Box 2)
      - County
        - Washtenaw 1959-1979 (Box 2)
      - Wayne, 1959-1979, Municipal
        - Ann Arbor 1964-1980 (Box 2)
        - Detroit 1961-1979 (Box 2)
        - Lansing 1963-1978 (Box 2)
        - Ypsilanti 1965 (Box 2)
    - Building
      - Michigan 1965-1979 (Box 2)
      - Laws
        - Michigan 1961-1977 (Box 2)
        - Ann Arbor and Washtenaw County 1948-1976, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Business
      - Michigan 1960-1979 (Box 2)
      - Districts
        - Michigan 1958-1979 (Box 2)
        - Ann Arbor 1956-1978 (Box 2)
        - Detroit 1956-1980 (Box 2)
        - Kalamazoo 1958-1964 (Box 2)
        - Lansing 1959-1967 (Box 2)
        - Pontiac 1962 (Box 2)
        - Ypsilanti 1957-1962 (Box 2)
  - C-F
    - Candidates 1964-1967 (Box 2)
    - Cemeteries 1960-1970 (Box 2)
    - Charities 1978 (Box 2)
    - Charters
      - Detroit 1970-1974 (Box 2)
      - Ann Arbor 1951-1974, 3 folders (Box 2)
      - Michigan 1964-1980 (Box 2)
    - Child Welfare
      - Ann Arbor 1976-1977 (Box 2)
      - Detroit 1959-1966 (Box 2)
      - Michigan 1939-1980, 3 folders (Box 2)
      - Washtenaw County 1952-1975 (Box 2)
    - Cities and Towns
      - Metropolitan Area 1950-1979 (Box 2)
      - Detroit 1957-1958 (Box 2)
      - Michigan (Box 3)
        - 1959 (Box 3)
        - 1952-1965 (Box 3)
        - 1948-1975 (Box 3)
      - Lansing 1977 (Box 3)
      - Planning
        - Michigan 1946-1979 (Box 3)
        - Ann Arbor 1942-1979, 5 folders (Box 3)
        - Detroit 1938-1977, 6 folders (Box 3)
        - East Lansing 1956-1965 (Box 3)
        - Lansing 1950-1972, 3 folders (Box 3)
        - Wayne 1967 (Box 3)
        - Ypsilanti 1942-1965, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - City Consolidation 1949-1959
    - City -- County Consolidation 1949-1966 (Box 3)
    - City -- Township Consolidation 1955-1979 (Box 3)
    - Civic Centers
      - Michigan 1955-1965 (Box 3)
      - Detroit 1960-1969 (Box 3)
      - Lansing 1952-1961 (Box 3)
    - Civic Organizations
      - Michigan 1943-1965 (Box 3)
      - Ann Arbor 1945-1965 (Box 3)
      - Detroit 1947-1965 (Box 3)
    - Civil Defense
      - Michigan 1950-1979, 4 folders (Box 3)
      - Ann Arbor and Washtenaw County 1950-1966 (Box 3)
      - Detroit and Wayne County 1950-1969 (Box 3)
      - Lansing Area and Ingham County 1950-1969 (Box 3)
    - Civil Liberties 1949-1977 (Box 4)
    - Civil Rights
      - Ann Arbor 1948-1974 (Box 4)
      - Michigan 1950-1980 (Box 4)
      - Detroit 1947-1971 (Box 4)
      - Lansing 1964-1971 (Box 4)
      - Ypsilanti 1962 (Box 4)
    - Civil Service
      - County
        - Michigan 1948-1965 (Box 4)
        - Washtenaw 1954-1961 (Box 4)
        - Wayne County 1940-1970 (Box 4)
      - Municipal
        - Michigan 1936-1968, 2 folders (Box 4)
        - Ann Arbor 1956-1969 (Box 4)
        - Detroit 1935-1970, 3 folders (Box 4)
      - Lansing 1954-1966 (Box 4)
      - State of Michigan 1938-1980, 13 folders (Box 4)
    - Colleges and Universities
      - Michigan
        - 1939-1957, 10 folders (Box 4)
        - 1957-1976, 5 folders (Box 5)
      - Delta College 1961-1964 (Box 5)
      - Eastern Michigan University 1962-1970 (Box 5)
      - Grand Valley State College 1961-1980 (Box 5)
      - Lansing, Ingham Community College 1964-1973 (Box 5)
      - Wayne County 1970-1971 (Box 5)
      - University of Michigan 1952-1971, 4 folders (Box 5)
      - Wayne State University, Finance 1955-1967 (Box 5)
    - Community Funds 1979 (Box 6)
    - Conflict of Interest 1946-1979 (Box 6)
    - Conservatism 1962-1964 (Box 6)
    - Communications
      - Ann Arbor 1972-1980, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Michigan 1966-1980, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Community and College, Ann Arbor, 19601-968 (Box 6)
    - Community Surveys, Ann Arbor 1956-1974 (Box 6)
    - Constitutional Conventions (Michigan) 1941-1979, 16 folders (Box 6)
    - Constitutions (State), Michigan 1944-1973, 7 folders (Box 7)
    - Consumers Protection 1959-1979 (Box 7)
    - Conventions 1959-1979 (Box 7)
    - Corrections
      - Michigan 1938-1980, 6 folders (Box 7)
      - Washtenaw County 1957-1968 (Box 7)
    - Coroners 1951-1968 (Box 7)
    - Corruption in Politics
      - Michigan 1927-1947, 14 folders
        - 1947-1975, 6 folders (Box 8)
      - Washtenaw County 1946 (Box 8)
    - Councils, Municipal -- Ann Arbor 1962-1976 (Box 8)
    - County Administration
      - Washtenaw County 1945-1958, 5 folders (Box 8)
      - Wayne County 1946-1956 (Box 8)
    - County Government
      - Michigan 1932-1980, 6 folders (Box 8)
      - Clinton County 1967-1968 (Box 8)
      - Gogebic County, 963-1967 (Box 8)
      - Ingham County 1950-1971 (Box 8)
      - Kent County 1947-1964 (Box 8)
      - Muskegon County 1947-1950 (Box 8)
      - Oakland County 1947-1976 (Box 8)
      - Wayne County 1936-1980, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Washtenaw County 1939-1980, 4 folders (Box 8)
    - County Planning
      - Michigan 1953-1965 (Box 8)
      - Oakland County 1959 (Box 8)
      - Washtenaw County 1941-1978 (Box 8)
      - Wayne County 1951-1965 (Box 8)
    - Courts
      - Michigan 1937-1967 (Box 8)
      - Wayne County 1951-1976, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Crime and Criminals
      - Michigan 1946-1980, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Ann Arbor 1970-1979 (Box 9)
      - Detroit 1946-1974 (Box 9)
    - Defense Areas 1941-1953, 1976, 9 folders (Box 9)
    - Defense Finance 1950-1974 (Box 9)
    - Defense Planning
      - Michigan 1940-1943, 6 folders (Box 9)
      - Ann Arbor and Washtenaw County 1941-1946, 5 folders (Box 9)
      - Detroit and Wayne County 1941-1950, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Discrimination in Employment 1948-1969, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Discrimination in Housing
      - Michigan 1948-1979, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Ann Arbor 1962-1967 (Box 9)
      - Detroit 1962-1970 (Box 9)
    - Domestic Relations 1965-1980 (Box 9)
    - Economic Conditions 1964-1980 (Box 9)
    - Economic Planning
      - Michigan 1944-1980, 4 folders (Box 9)
      - Detroit 1944-1958 (Box 10)
    - Education
      - Michigan 1935-1977, 6 folders (Box 10)
      - Washtenaw County 1962-1968 (Box 10)
      - Ann arbor 1964-1977 (Box 10)
      - Finance
        - Michigan 1935-1979, 13 folders (Box 10)
        - Washtenaw County 1970-1980 (Box 10)
    - Elections
      - State -- Michigan
        - 1937-October 1948, 11 folders (Box 10)
        - October 1948 – 1978, 17 folders (Box 11)
      - County
        - Michigan 1950-1966 (Box 11)
        - Washtenaw County 1947-1963, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Wayne County 1946-1979, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Local -- Michigan 1956-1968 (Box 11)
      - Municipal
        - Michigan 1947-1969, 3 folders (Box 11)
        - Ann Arbor 1946-1977, 6 folders (Box 12)
        - Dearborn 1950-1959 (Box 12)
        - Detroit 1935-1973, 9 folders (Box 12)
        - Grand Rapids 1947-1964 (Box 12)
        - Lansing 1950-1971, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Ypsilanti 1950-1965 (Box 12)
      - Township -- Michigan 1947-1979 (Box 12)
      - Funds 1956-1979, 3 folders (Box 12)
      - Laws 1952-1979 (Box 12)
    - Employment
      - Michigan 1942-1979, 3 folders (Box 12)
      - Washtenaw County 1975-1976 (Box 12)
      - Ann Arbor 1945-1975 (Box 12)
      - Detroit 1945-1975 (Box 12)
    - Energy -- Power Resources 1979 (Box 12)
    - Environment 1971-1986 (Box 12)
    - Escheats 1955-1979 (Box 12)
    - Fairs 1943-1966, 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Federal Aid 1945-1977 (Box 12)
    - Finance
      - State of Michigan 1932-1979, 27 folders (Box 13)
      - Local 1947-1967 (Box 13)
      - County
        - Michigan 1946-1965 (Box 13)
        - Ingham County 1950-1962 (Box 13)
        - Kent County 1947-1962 (Box 13)
        - Washtenaw County 1934-1976, 3 folders (Box 13)
        - Wayne County 1936-1967 (Box 13)
      - Municipal
        - Michigan 1941-1964, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Ann Arbor 1943-1978 (Box 13)
        - Detroit
          - 1935-1945, 2 folders (Box 14)
            (non-municipal)
          - Dodge Report 1957 (Box 14)
          - 1950-1976, 3 folders (Box 14)
        - Lansing 1952-1970 (Box 14)
        - Ypsilanti 1950-1967 (Box 14)
    - Fire Departments
      - Ann Arbor 1960-1979 (Box 14)
      - Detroit 1949-1966 (Box 14)
      - Lansing 1962 (Box 14)
    - Fire Protection
      - Ann Arbor 1945-1962 (Box 14)
      - Michigan 1947-1977 (Box 14)
      - Washtenaw County 1947-1962 (Box 14)
    - Firearms 1968-1976 (Box 14)
    - Fiscal Administration 1947-1980, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Flood Control 1948-1970 (Box 14)
    - Forests and Forestry 1941-1979 (Box 14)
    - Foundations and Institutions 1947-1977 (Box 14)
  - G-L
    - Gambling 1938-1980, 5 folders (Box 14)
    - Government Contracts 1943-1962 (Box 14)
    - Government Liability 1961-1965 (Box 14)
    - Governmental Research
      - Michigan 1939-1962 (Box 14)
      - Bureaus
        - Detroit 1944-1960 (Box 14)
        - Michigan 1936-1963 (Box 14)
    - Governors -- Michigan 1963-1975, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Handicapped 1944-1980 (Box 14)
    - Harbors
      - Michigan 1944-1959 (Box 14)
      - Detroit 1940-1971, 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Highways
      - Michigan
        - 1935-December 1950, 2 folders (Box 14)
        - December 1950-1979, 5 folders (Box 15)
      - Washtenaw County 1949-1979, 3 folders (Box 15)
      - Detroit (Metropolitan Area) 1954-1979 (Box 15)
      - Lansing 1964-1965 (Box 15)
      - Finance -- Washtenaw County 1946-1969 (Box 15)
      - Zoning 1960 (Box 15)
    - Historical Markers 1962-1964 (Box 15)
    - Home Rule 1945-1973, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Hospitals
      - Michigan
        - 1935-May 1958, 15 folders (Box 15)
        - June 1958-1968, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Ann Arbor 1971-1972 (Box 16)
      - Detroit (Metropolitan Area) 1945-1979, 3 folders (Box 16)
      - Ypsilanti 1954-1964 (Box 16)
    - Housing
      - Michigan 1938-1979, 7 folders (Box 16)
      - Ann Arbor 1939-1978, 5 folders (Box 16)
      - Detroit 1938-1980, 9 folders (Box 16)
      - Lansing 1952-1979 (Box 16)
      - Washtenaw County 1950-1975 (Box 16)
    - Income 1953-1979 (Box 16)
    - Industrial Districts
      - Michigan 1951-1962 (Box 16)
      - Washtenaw County 1960-1962 (Box 16)
    - Industrial Waste 1977-1980 (Box 16)
    - Information Processing Systems
      - Michigan 1965-1979 (Box 16)
      - Municipal 1965 (Box 16)
    - Initiative and Referendum 1948-1965 (Box 16)
    - Inspection 1943-1965 (Box 16)
    - Insurance
      - Michigan 1946-1978 (Box 16)
      - Fire 1965 (Box 16)
      - Governmental 1944-1979 (Box 16)
      - Health 1949-1979 (Box 16)
      - Motor Vehicles 1957-1979, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Old Age 1950-1962 (Box 16)
    - Intergovernmental Relations 1953-1980, 3 folders
      - Michigan 1972-1980 (Box 17)
      - Ann Arbor 1973-1979 (Box 17)
      - Washtenaw County 1975 (Box 17)
    - Judges 1947-1980, 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Justice, Administration of 1946-1980, 4 folders (Box 17)
    - Justices of the Peace 1950-1969 (Box 17)
    - Juvenile Courts
      - Michigan 1950-1979 (Box 17)
      - Washtenaw County 1954-1974 (Box 17)
      - Detroit 1951-1957 (Box 17)
    - Juvenile Delinquency
      - Michigan 1943-1979, 4 folders (Box 17)
      - Detroit 1951-1957 (Box 17)
    - Labor Administration
      - Michigan 1950-1967, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Detroit 1947-1965 (Box 17)
      - Washtenaw County 1956-1966 (Box 17)
    - Labor and Laboring Classes 1965-1979 (Box 17)
    - Labor Unions 1946-1971, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Land Use
      - Michigan 1946-1979 (Box 17)
      - Washtenaw County 1977 (Box 17)
    - Laws, Statutes, etc. 1964-1980, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Legal Aid 1965-1978 (Box 17)
    - Legislative Reference Service 1941-1971 (Box 17)
    - Legislatures
      - Michigan
        - 1939-June 1952, 9 folders (Box 17)
        - June 1952-February 1964, 26 folders (Box 18)
        - February 1964 – 1980, 22 folders (Box 19)
      - Apportionment 1964-1980, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Librarians 1961 (Box 19)
    - Libraries
      - Michigan 1935-1980, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - University of Michigan 1950-1968 (Box 19)
      - Ann Arbor 1953-1973 (Box 19)
      - Detroit 1949-1979 (Box 19)
      - Lansing 1959-1968 (Box 19)
      - Michigan State University 1953-1965 (Box 19)
      - Washtenaw County 1960-1967 (Box 19)
      - Ypsilanti 1960-1966 (Box 19)
      - State Aid 1958-1962 (Box 19)
      - Special 1956-1961 (Box 19)
    - Licenses 1947-1979, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Liquor Traffic
      - Michigan 1935-1979, 15 folders (Box 20)
      - Ann Arbor 1962-1978 (Box 20)
      - Ypsilanti and Township 1962 (Box 20)
    - Local Government 1946-1979 (Box 20)
    - Location of Industry
      - Michigan 1949-1967, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Detroit 1950-1957 (Box 20)
      - Lansing 1960 (Box 20)
  - M-R
    - Medical Care
      - Michigan 1942-1979, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Washtenaw County 1966-1967 (Box 20)
    - Mental Defectives 1943-1956, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Mental Health 1954-1977, 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Metropolitan Planning
      - Michigan 1947-1979 (Box 20)
      - Ann Arbor 1952-1971 (Box 20)
      - Battle Creek 1951-1966 (Box 20)
      - Detroit 1945-1979, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Flint 1957-1960 (Box 20)
      - Grand Rapids 1947-1959, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Lansing 1952-1959 (Box 20)
      - Ypsilanti 1954-1957 (Box 20)
    - Michigan 1943-1957 (Box 20)
    - Migrants
      - General 1950-1965 (Box 20)
      - Michigan 1947-1979, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Military Administration 1964-1970 (Box 21)
    - Military Service 1942-1968, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Milk 1941-1967, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Mines and Mineral Resources 1941-1980 (Box 21)
    - Minorities
      - Michigan 1948-1979, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Detroit 1953-1965 (Box 21)
    - Motor Boats 1956-1977 (Box 21)
    - Motor Vehicle Drivers 1966-1969 (Box 21)
    - Motor Vehicles
      - Michigan 1943-1978, 4 folders (Box 21)
      - Government Use 1942-1974 (Box 21)
    - Municipal Administration
      - Michigan 1947-1955 (Box 21)
      - Ann Arbor 1946-1958, 9 folders (Box 21)
      - Dearborn 1947-1961, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Detroit 1946-1958, 6 folders (Box 21)
      - Grand Rapids 1947-1954, 15 folders (Box 21)
    - Municipal Courts
      - Michigan 1947-1969 (Box 22)
      - Ann Arbor 1943-1967 (Box 22)
      - Detroit 1945-1962 (Box 22)
    - Municipal Government
      - Michigan 1938-1979, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Allen Park 1956-1961 (Box 22)
      - Ann Arbor 1938-1973, 6 folders (Box 22)
      - Bay City 1950-1961 (Box 22)
      - Battle Creek 1950-1966 (Box 22)
      - Berkely 1952-1957 (Box 22)
      - Birmingham 1952-1957 (Box 22)
      - Detroit 1941-1979, 4 folders (Box 22)
      - East Ann Arbor 1945-1956 (Box 22)
      - East Detroit 1951 (Box 22)
      - East Lansing 1952-1968 (Box 22)
      - Flint 1932-1967 (Box 22)
      - Garden City 1957-1960 (Box 22)
      - Grand Rapids 1948-1966, 3 folders (Box 22)
      - Hamtramck 1939-1963 (Box 22)
      - Harbor Springs 1953 (Box 22)
      - Harper Woods 1953-1961 (Box 22)
      - Highland Park 1953-1965 (Box 22)
      - Hudson 1961 (Box 22)
      - Iron Mountain 1951 (Box 22)
      - Jackson 1946-1961 (Box 22)
      - Lansing 1950-1972, 4 folders (Box 22)
      - Lathrup City 1953-1958 (Box 23)
      - Livonia 1950-1960 (Box 23)
      - Madison Heights 1950-1959 (Box 23)
      - Milan 1955-1957 (Box 23)
      - Mount Clemens 1962 (Box 23)
      - Pleasant Ridge 1956-1962 (Box 23)
      - Plymouth 1953-1958 (Box 23)
      - Pontiac 1944-1970 (Box 23)
      - Port Huron 1952-1955 (Box 23)
      - Riverview 1958-1961 (Box 23)
      - Roseville 1953-1961 (Box 23)
      - St. Clair Shores 1952-1957 (Box 23)
      - Saline 1946-1962 (Box 23)
      - Southfield 1955-1961 (Box 23)
      - Southgate 1955-1960 (Box 23)
      - Trenton 1955-1960 (Box 23)
      - Troy 1955-1960 (Box 23)
      - Warrren 1955-1960 (Box 23)
      - Wayne 1952-1960 (Box 23)
      - Ypsilanti 1947-1973, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Municipal Incorporation 1952-1967 (Box 23)
    - Municipal League 1941-1963 (Box 23)
    - Narcotics
      - Michigan 1952-1967 (Box 23)
      - Ann Arbor 1970-1977 (Box 23)
      - Detroit 1972-1975 (Box 23)
    - Natural Resources 1939-1980, 9 folders (Box 23)
    - Negroes
      - Michigan 1947-1971 (Box 23)
      - Detroit 1943-1962 (Box 23)
    - Nuisances 1975 (Box 23)
    - Obscenity 1962-1977 (Box 23)
    - Oil and Gas 1936-1975, 3 folders (Box 23)
    - Old Age
      - Michigan 1947-1978, 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Washtenaw County 1947-1959 (Box 23)
      - Wayne County 1962-1970 (Box 23)
    - Olympic Games 1963-1966 (Box 23)
    - Ordinances
      - Ann Arbor 1958-1973 (Box 23)
      - Detroit 1965 (Box 23)
      - East Lansing 1953 (Box 23)
      - Ypsilanti 1957-1962 (Box 23)
      - Ypsilanti Township 1960 (Box 23)
    - Parking
      - Michigan 1947-1965 (Box 24)
      - Ann Arbor 1946-1976, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Detroit 1947-1979, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - East Lansing 1951-1965 (Box 24)
      - Grand Rapids 1948-1961 (Box 24)
      - Lansing 1950-1968, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Pontiac 1947-1956 (Box 24)
      - Ypsilanti 1952-1961 (Box 24)
    - Parks
      - Michigan 1927-1980, 5 folders (Box 24)
      - Sleeping Bear Dunes 1961-1979 (Box 24)
      - Washtenaw County 1960-1978, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Detroit 1951-1975 (Box 24)
    - Pensions, Civil
      - Michigan 1936-1979, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Detroit 1938-1965 (Box 24)
      - Lansing 1950-1979 (Box 24)
      - Roseville 1958 (Box 24)
    - Pensions, Industrial 1949-1965 (Box 24)
    - Police
      - Michigan 1950-1977, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - State -- Michigan 1940-1980, 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Ann Arbor 1951-1980, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Detroit 1937-1980, 5 folders (Box 24)
    - Political Parties
      - Michigan
        - 1939 – February 1946, 8 folders (Box 24)
        - February 1946 – April 1965, 30 folders (Box 25)
        - April 1965 – 1980, 7 folders (Box 26)
      - Ingham County 1962-1967 (Box 26)
      - Macomb County 1962-1966 (Box 26)
      - Washtenaw County 1955-1977 (Box 26)
      - Wayne County 1962-1966 (Box 26)
    - Public Utilities 1975-1980 (Box 26)
    - Railroads 1964-1979, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Refuse and Refuse Disposal
      - Michigan 1948-1980 (Box 26)
      - Ann Arbor and Washtenaw County 1942-1978, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Detroit and Wayne County 1939-1980 (Box 26)
      - Lansing and Ingham County 1953-1973 (Box 26)
    - Regional Planning 1931-1947 (Box 26)
  - S-Z
    - Strikes
      - Michigan 1946-1975, 3 folders (Box 26)
      - Detroit 1946-1979, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Subversive Activities 1947-1963, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Swimming Pools 1958-1960 (Box 26)
    - Tax Administration 1941-1964 (Box 26)
    - Tax Allocations
      - Michigan 1946-1973, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Washtenaw County 1953-1962 (Box 26)
    - Tax Delinquency 1949-1955 (Box 26)
    - Tax Exemptions 1948-1979 (Box 26)
    - Taxation
      - Income -- Municipal 1966-1973, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Inheritance 1966 (Box 26)
      - Intangibles 1956-1967 (Box 26)
      - Liquor 1962-1965 (Box 26)
      - Michigan 1964-1972 (Box 26)
      - Municipal
        - Detroit 1955-1970 (Box 26)
        - Lansing 1964-1966 (Box 26)
      - Severance 1962 (Box 26)
      - Property 1971-1975 (Box 26)
      - State 1934 – 1980, 42 folders (Box 27)
      - Local 1948-1976 (Box 28)
      - County -- Washtenaw County 1964-1980 (Box 28)
      - Municipal
        - Ann Arbor 1933-1980, 3 folders (Box 28)
        - Detroit 1943-1960 (Box 28)
        - Saginaw 1951 (Box 28)
      - Business 1953-1979, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Chain Store 1954-1968 (Box 28)
      - Income
        - State 1952-1980 (Box 28)
        - Municipal
          - Michigan 1955-1966 (Box 28)
          - Ann Arbor 1972-1974 (Box 28)
          - Detroit 1960-1969, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Tax Limitation 1948-1980 (Box 28)
      - Motor Fuels 1951-1979 (Box 28)
      - Motor Vehicles 1955-1979 (Box 28)
      - Property
        - Ann Arbor 1960-1980 (Box 28)
        - Detroit 1957-1979 (Box 28)
        - Michigan 1942-1980, 4 folders (Box 28)
        - Washtenaw County 1956-1979 (Box 28)
        - Wayne County 1962-1979 (Box 28)
      - Public Utility 1962-1965 (Box 28)
      - Sales 1947-1980, 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Taxpayers' Associations 1968-1975 (Box 28)